<?xml version="1.0"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="secure.xsl"?><blog>	<!-- <post>		<categories>			<category>				twitter			</category>		</categories>		<title></title>		<text>			<section>				I think my code broke at work today because it misses me. #rebeliousteenagers 			</section>		</text>		<images>			<image></image>		</images>		<links>			<link>			</link>		</links>		<date>			2011/12/04		</date>		<time>			6:41 am		</time>	</post> -->	<post>		<categories>			<category>				blog			</category>		</categories>		<title>Whats the point</title>		<text>			<section>				Lets face it... I am not good at keeping up a blog. If you read this ever, let me know... Shibberjitts@yahoo.com			</section>		</text>		<images>			<image></image>		</images>		<links>			<link>			</link>		</links>		<date>			2012/4/3		</date>		<time>			9:35 pm		</time>	</post>	<post>		<categories>			<category>				blog			</category>		</categories>		<title>Merry Christmas</title>		<text>			<section>				What a wonderful time of year. Friends, family... games, and food. I am very thankful for the people in my life. For the love of my church family, and the life I share with my wife.			</section>		</text>		<images>			<image></image>		</images>		<links>			<link>			</link>		</links>		<date>			2011/12/26		</date>		<time>			7:17 am		</time>	</post>	<post>		<categories>			<category>twitter</category>		</categories>		<text>			<section>My first christmas bonus #ThankYou</section>		</text>		<date>2011/12/13</date>		<time>4:42 pm</time>	</post>	<post>		<categories>			<category>facebook</category>		</categories>		<text>			<section>Ladies and Gentlemen, I have changed my car's serpentine belt which made me find the broken tensioner pulley which I also replaced. Total cost is about 50 dollars. Total man points is around +34. My car lives on!</section>		</text>		<date>2011/12/10</date>		<time>6:23 pm</time>	</post>	<post>		<categories>			<category>facebook</category>		</categories>		<text>			<section>I recently watched both the media and viral videos of the UC David protest and it's just one bad situation. I wasn't there so my judgement means nothing but surrounding cops just doesn't seem like a good idea.</section>		</text>		<date>2011/12/06</date>		<time>9:48 am</time>	</post>	<post>		<categories>			<category>blog</category>			<category>blueSquare</category>		</categories>		<title>Operation Menu Freefall</title>		<text>			<section>I'm not very good at staying focused when it comes to hobby activities. I might not post regularly for the next couple of days because I'm trying to create a menu system for blueSquare. I just don't like standard menu left menu right menus and that goes double for  this website which should be constant interaction.</section>			<section>There are so many ideas that I have to make this a great site. I just need to tackle them one at a time.</section>		</text>		<date>2011/12/05</date>		<time>3:17 pm</time>	</post>	<post>		<categories>			<category>blog</category>		</categories>		<title>My Toaster :(</title>		<images>			<image>blog/toaster.png</image>		</images>		<date>2011/12/04</date>		<time>11:14 am</time>	</post> 	<post>		<categories>			<category>twitter</category>		</categories>		<title></title>		<text>			<section>I think my code broke at work today because it misses me. @rebeliousteenagers</section>		</text>		<date>2011/12/04</date>		<time>6:41 am</time>	</post>	<post>		<categories>			<category>blueSquare</category>		</categories>		<title>Blog data now in XML file</title>		<text>			<section>This blog instead of being hard coded is now run from a xml document which makes life for myself a lot easier. This is step two for the conversation... section of this website. The next step is to place a html page between the blog page and the actual call to the xml file. The idea is that this will add slightly more security to this site and allow me to secure posts. But in the end I will mostly do all of this so that I may edit and view my posts online without them "appearing" live to everyone else.</section>			<section>This post also starts something I should do with my previous "blueFirend" post and explain my actions: "How and Why".			</section>		</text>		<links>			<link title="The How and Why">/project/xmlData</link>		</links>		<date>2011/12/02</date>		<time>10:10 pm</time>	</post>	<post>		<categories>			<category>blueSquare</category>		</categories>		<title>Welcome my new little buddy! :)</title>		<text>			<section>I am pleased to announce the newest member of blueSquare: "blueFriend"! Just middle click on your mouse and he'll come chancing after your pointer until you hover over an item.</section>			<section>In the future he will provide explanation to why I made the site the way I did... and his color needs altered. But for now... enjoy his silent company</section>		</text>		<date>2011/12/01</date>		<time>12:01 am</time>	</post>	<post>		<categories>			<category>blueSquare</category>		</categories>		<title>Blog List Design Is Done</title>		<text>			<section>I Have finished the simple design for blueSquare's conversation piece. I can't really call this a blog section because I know that all of my thoughts are not long enough to be what I would classify as a "blog" post. Which is why I will be supporting:</section>			<section>Blog posts, Tweets or "Short posts", Facebook Comments, BlueSquare site updates, and Recycled web posts. This will allow me a way to classify my posts.</section>			<section>I will also be looking into the idea of including a "month" category so that people can cut down on what they initially see. Also a type category will be needed for most blog and web recycle posts so that I can show inportant items to those who want to see important items and vise vera.</section>		</text>		<date>2011/29/11</date>		<time>9:30 pm</time>	</post>	<post>		<categories>			<category>twitter</category>		</categories>		<title></title>		<text>			<section>I am a muppet! @TheMuppetMovie</section>		</text>		<date>2011/29/11</date>		<time>9:30 pm</time>	</post></blog>